onesystemcare.com 2019-05-04

# One System Care - Privacy Policy

Welcome to One System Care Limited website. Using our website and the Software we offer, is subject to the Terms of Use of the website at  http://onesystemcare.com/terms  , and to the terms of this Privacy Policy. By using this website and/or the Software we provide, you hereby agree to all the terms. 

Should you have any questions or comments concerning this policy, or if you wish to know which data we have collected about you, you may contact us at: [ support@onesystemcare.com ](mailto:support@onesystemcare.com) . 

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. All updates will be published at our website and are affective upon publishing them in the website. 

Upon clicking on the call-to-action button (such as "Register" or "Clean Now") you will be - required to fill a form in which you are required to provide your name, address, email, and payment method. 

If you are under 18 years of age, please avoid using this website and do not use our software. 

You may receive email messages from us, from time to time, relating to our Software, referral links, software activation information, support links, upgrades for the software full version with updates included. 

We may collect some information relating to you including among others your IP Address, browser type, operating system version, GUID, customer configuration, the identification number of the hardware used by you, whether you are Administrator or not, version of the operating system and service pack and whether your Windows operating system is 32 or 64 bit, internal tracking identifiers that we use to track downloads, installs, sales, and uninstalls, your using behavior of our Software, and the type and number of files located by our Software in your computer. 

Such information we collect may be used to carry out our service, as well as for newsletters to you, personalization of your user experience with our Software, marketing and remarketing, research and development of our Software, for notifying you of new services and products we may offer, and changes to the Software and our existing services and products. 

Our software, when downloaded, includes third party software that collects browsing, non-identifiable information, and behavioral preferences - by adding tracking technology (cookies) that tracks the content you have viewed and suggests you accordingly, advertisements that might interest you. Note that you may reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent - but such settings alterations may affect the functionality of our Software. If you wish to stop sharing any of your information, please uninstall our software and do not use the website. Information collected prior to such uninstall will still be kept with us and may be used by us, as used prior to such uninstall. 

Our Website and our newsletter may include various links to third party websites or promote third party products. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties in any way. 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, or if you believe that our website is not following its stated Privacy Policy, please contact us through our Contact Us page.
